wpstand.com 2017-11-19

# WPStand Privacy Policy

To maintain the privacy of WPStand’s visitor is our utmost concern, the site is providing quality information about all WordPress issues as well as the site is also managing the privacy and safety of the visitors.

Personal information of the users such as your name, Email address, postal code and other information that would be the part of your registration process will not be mentioned publically.  To maintain the privacy of the users and to keep the information confidential is our one the most important values.

**Site Activity Data**

When a visitor visits the WPStand.com, the web server of the website gets started the collection of logged information automatically, that included the TCP or IP address, time, data and the files accessed by the visitor. This type of information is kept by the site for a certain time period. The purpose of this type of information just used for the site administration and for the better performance of the website, and never be disclosed to the third party in any case.

**Cookies**

The browser you are using can store the cookies of the website that can give you more communicating experience with WP Stand. This service would be interesting for you to customize our data to match with your requirements. The site will never disclose the cookies and personal information in any way without your permission.

**Website Visitors**

The site administrator collects the non-personal information about the visitor such as the web browsers type, referring site, language preference, country or region, date and the time of each visitor. To collect this non-personal information is to identify the region of the visitor and to determine the performance of the site and this type of information never disclosed and keep for a specific period of time.

**Ads**

The ads on the websites may be brought the user’s data by their partners who are organizing the advertising on the websites, who would set the cookies. These cookies are attached with the add server to recognize computer every time and these server send online advertisement to compile the information about the computer. This information used by the ad networks to allow them to show the advertisements that they believes you are more interested. However the information never be misused and disclosed in any case.

**Comments**

The information such as your email address and your social profile data you give while commenting on our site, but these should not be spam will never be disclosed. So you can share your views freely about the content on our site.

**Privacy Policy Revisions**

The modification in the privacy polices of WP Stand, you will be informed immediately through email. Still, you have to keep in mind how we are handling previously collected information of our users.
